University Relations, Office of; Records ua760
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of University Relations Records
1960-1999
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Office of University Relations
ua760
36.5 cubic ft.
Contains records form the Office of University Relations and its predecessors, including the Office of Public Relations and Office of Community Relations.
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has been organized into five series. The first series is made up of subject files and administrative files maintained by the office. The second series includes press releases that the office produced from various publications. The third series includes a file of publications produced by the office for various entities throughout the University. The fourth series documents the schools athletic teams. The fifth series is made up of photographs and photographic materials, while the sixth and final series is made up of press clippings that the office retained from various publications.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials created by the Office of University Relations and several of its predecessor and subordinate offices, including: the Office of Community Relations, the Public Relations Office, and the News Bureau.
Materials include: University publications; press releases; clippings; CRO logs; sports files that include press releases, season schedules, brochures, statistics, and clippings; and budget files.
Historical Note
The University's Public Relations Office, responsible for press releases and public information, was created circa 1961. In the late 1960s, it became the Office of Community Relations, which was incorporated into the newly-formed Office of University Affairs in 1972. The title changed again when it became the Office of University Relations (sometime prior to 1985), although, somewhat confusingly, there was a brief period in the 1990s when the Office of Community Relations was reintroduced and existed alongside the Office of University Relations. From 1990 through circa 2005, the Office of University Relations was administered by the Division of University Advancement. As of 2017, public information and media relations are managed by the Office of Communications and Marketing.
public relations; News Clippings; Press releases.; UAlbany Communications & Marketing
- Subject and Administrative Files, 1961-1995; 4.5 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Files in this series have been ordered based upon original box labels.
  Scope and Contents
  This series is made up of subject files the office maintained on university events that it promoted, such as research conferences, speaking engagements, building dedications and artistic performances. This series contains files as well on individuals and organizations that the office had contact with, inluding legislators and student groups. These files contain press releases, copies of advertisements placed in local publications as well as correspondence.
  This series also contains administrative records maintained by the Office. These mostly include office memoranda related to events covered by the office.
  - Dedication Events, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dedication Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dedication of Joseph Henry Physics Building, 1968 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dedication of Joseph Henry Physics Building, 1968 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dedication '69 Publication Material, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Special Events at SUNYA, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dedication Weekend, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dedication of the Agnes E. Futterer Lounge, PAC, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dedication-Biological Sciences Building, 1968 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dedication-Chemistry Bldg, 1967 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dedication- Chemistry Building Dedication, 1971 April (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dedication Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on Dedication of SUNYA, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SAMPLES-ARRANGEMENTS for dedication weekend, 1969 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dedication-Budget, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agenda Minutes(Campus Dedication), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dedication Printing, Etc., 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dedication-Education Bldg., 1967 November (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Education Build., Dedication, 1967 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dedication of Humanities Bldg.-Cassette, 1973 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Edith O. Wallace Dedication of Humanities Bldg., 1973 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dedication-Humanities Bldg., 1973 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dedication- Performing Arts Center, 1969 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dedication- Univ. Library, 1968 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Library Dedication, 1968 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dedication-UL, 1968 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dedication '69(alumni), Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dedication '69(guide to symposium topics), Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dedication '69(anniversary material), Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - School of Business-Dedication Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dedication School of Business Bldg., 1968 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Community-University Day, 1974 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Community-University Day, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Community Day at the University, 1973 October 13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Open House (Community-University ), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Louis T. Benezet Inauguration, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Russian Educators, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clipping Collection University Council, Deans and Directors, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Unit Printing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Community Relation Annual Report, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, Collection, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Office of Community Relations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Community Relations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Community Relations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Draft Resistance, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SDS Conference, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Seminar on Scientific Revolution & Its Impact on Man and Society, 1968 March 17-1968 March 21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Protest on Draft 4-Univ. President's Memo, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Campus Crisis, 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Moratorium, 1969 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kent 25: Moratorium, 1970 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam War + SUNYA, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Racism Violence at State, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - SDS(Students for a Democratic Society), 1965-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - SUNYA 128th Opening Convocation, 1971 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Speech by Dr.Kuusisto, Faculty Meeting, 1969 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ethnic Survey, 1971; 1973 March (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Center for Science the future of Human Affairs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - SUNY New Releases, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - SUNYA Student Association Supreme Court, Decision on the Bias Appropriation to Washington D.C., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Office of Community Relations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Collins, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - College of Arts Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Central Administration, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - C, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - B, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Atmospheric Science Research Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Atmospheric Science Research Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Athletic Facilities, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - A, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Monthly Reports to Chancellor Gould, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities; News Clippings, 1968 September-1968 December (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1975 January-1975 February (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1975 February-1975 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1975 July-1975 November (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1975 November-1975 December (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - SUNY Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1975 December-1976 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SUNY Monthly Report of Campus Activities, 1976 May-1976 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - SUNYA, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fuller Road Property, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Emphasis Specials, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commercial Printing Charges, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Luncheons, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Dinner December, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Dinner, 1973 March (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Breakfast, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Focus, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Military Historians Mtg., 1975 August 10 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Science Symposium, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - School of Education, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - U, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - University Centers, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - University College, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - V, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vice President for Management + Planning, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Vice President for Research, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - W, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Community Relation Office-Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Legislators, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Deans & Directors, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Allen Center(Cont.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Milne School, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - G.E. College Bowl, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hearing Committee, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Barney Fowler- Sayles Hall Case, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Barney Fowler- Sayles Hall, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Calendar of Events, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Deans and Directors- Memos to, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Calendar of Events, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Calendar of Events, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - NYS Government Public, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - F, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Flag Ceremony, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Tisdale, Walter M., Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Basketball '78, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Football 1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Football Statistics, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Professional Services Titles, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Student Association, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - University Forum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - University Opinionnaire, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - SUNY-Wide Campus Activity Reports, 1978 January-1978 March (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - SUNY-Wide Campus Activity Reports, 1977 December-1978 January (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - SUNY-Wide Campus Activity Reports, 1978 March-1978 May (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - SUNY-Wide News Clippings, 1978 May-1978 July (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - SUNY-Wide Press Clippings, 1978 September-1978 October (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - SUNY-Wide Press Clippings, 1978 July-1978 August (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - SUNY-Wide Press Clippings, 1978 August-1978 September (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - SUNY-Wide Press Clippings, 1978 October-1978 November (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - SUNY-Wide Press Clippings, 1978 November-1978 December (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - VHS-Maya Angelou [Unreadable] with Songbird Article (Box 5, Vhs 1)
  - State University of New York Press Release(Thurlow terrace), 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases prepared by Alumni affairs which we sent out, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - June, News Releases, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Community Relations- Temporary Appointment, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SUNY Special Report, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Agram, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Benezet, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kuusisto, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - N, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - S, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - R, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Harpers Magazine, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - EOP, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - E, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Institute on Man and Science Rensselaerville, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - J, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - L, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - G, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - M, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Press Releases, 1961-1995; 4.5 cubic ft.
  This series is made up of press releases issued by the Office and its predecessors. The vast majority of this series is made up of chronological files maintained by the office of press releases, with some of these files also containing press clippings.
  Files in this series have been maintained in their original order upon transfer. Files in this series were arranged chronologically, [with duplicate files placed at the end?].
  - Guide to SUNY News Press Releases, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1961 January (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1961 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1961 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1961 July (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1961 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1961 September (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1961 October (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1961 November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1961 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1962 January (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1962 February (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1962 March (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1962 April (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1962 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1962 June (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1962 July (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1962 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1962 September (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1962 October (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1962 November (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1962 December (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1963 February (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1963 March (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases, 1963 April (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1963 May (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1963 June (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1963 July (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1963 August (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1964 September (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Press Releases, 1964 October (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Press Releases, 1964 November (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1964 December (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Press Releases, 1965 January (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1965 February (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Press Releases, 1965 March (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1965 April (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Press Releases, 1965 May (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1965 June (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1965 July (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1965 August (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 1965 September (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1965 October (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1965 November (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 1965 December (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, 1966 January (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Press Releases, 1966 February (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Press Releases, 1966 March (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Press Releases, 1966 April (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Press Releases, 1966 May (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Press Releases, 1966 June (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Press Releases, 1966 July (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Press Releases, 1966 August (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Press Releases, 1966 September (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Press Releases, 1966 October (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Press Releases, 1966 November (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Press Releases, 1966 December (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Public Relations Office, 1966 December (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - News Clippings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Press Releases, 1967 January (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Press Releases, 1967 February (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Press Releases, 1967 March (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Press Releases, 1967 April (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Press Releases, 1967 May (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Press Releases, 1967 June (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Press Releases, 1967 July (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Press Releases, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1967 October (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1967 November (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1967 December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1968 January (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1968 February (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1968 March (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1968 April (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1968 July (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1968 August (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1968 September (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1968 October (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1968 November (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SUNYA News, 1968 December (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1969 January (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1969 February (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1969 March (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1969 April (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1969 May (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1969 June (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1969 August (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1969 September (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1969 October (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases, 1969 November (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1970 January (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1970 February (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1970 March (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Press Releases, 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Press Releases, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1970 July (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Press Releases, 1970 August (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1970 September (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Press Releases, 1970 October (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1970 November (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Press Releases, 1970 December (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1971 February (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1971 March (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 1971 April (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1971 May (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1971 June (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 1971 July (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Press Releases, 1971 September (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Press Releases, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Press Releases, 1971 November (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Press Releases, 1971 December (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1972 January (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1972 February (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1972 March (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1972 April (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1972 May (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1972 June (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1972 July (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1972 August (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1972 September (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1972 October (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1972 November (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1973 January (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1973 February (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1973 March (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1973 May (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1973 June (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1973 July (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1973 August (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1973 September (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1973 November (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1973 December (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, 1973 September 12 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1974 January (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1974 February (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1974 April (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1974 May (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Press Releases, 1974 June (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Press Releases, 1974 July (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Press Releases, 1974 September (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1974 October (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Press Releases, 1974 November (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Press Releases, 1975 January (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1975 February (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1975 March (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1975 April (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 1975 May (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1975 June (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1975 July (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 1975 August (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, 1975 September (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Press Releases, 1975 October (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1975 November (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1975 December (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1976 January (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1976 February (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1976 March (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1976 April (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1976 May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1976 July (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1976 August (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1976 September (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1976 October (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 1976 November (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1977 February (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1977 May (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1977 June (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1977 August (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1978 September (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1979 May (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1982 September (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Press Releases, 1984 January (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Press Releases, 1984 May (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases, 1984 June (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases, 1984 July (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1984 August (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1984 September (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases, 1984 October (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1984 November (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Press Releases, 1984 December (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Degree Recipients, 1984 December (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Press Releases, 1985 January (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1985 February (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Press Releases, 1985 March (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 1985 April (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Degree Recipients, 1985 May (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1985 May (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases, 1985 June (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1985 July (Box 4, Folder 42)